Omima Khaled Ghanem

Frontend Developer

GitHub ► Portfolio

PROFILE

I am a Frontend Developer with +1 year of experience in frontend development technologies.

I use **JavaScript** and **React.js** as a main framework.

Familiar with Angular, Node.js and MongoDB.

Able to integrate frontend with backend and work with APIs.

Very Passionate about creating elegant user interfaces, that are **responsive to all screens**.

Able to convert any Design on **Figma** or **AdobeXD** to a responsive interactive website.

EDUCATION

Information Technology Institute (ITI) - Ministry of Communication andAug 2022 - Nov 2022Information Technology (MCIT)Alexandria, Egypt

Frontend Development - Intensive Code Camp (ICC)

Kafr El-Shiekh University. 2014 – 2018

Bachelor of Agricultural Engineering

Professional Experience

Workiom *⊘* Dec 2023 – present

Frontend Developer | Angular

At Valinteca *∂* Dec 2022 – Dec 2023

Frontend Developer

SKILLS

JavaScript
Redux
Redux

Next.js
Angular
Tailwind css
Bootstrap5

• HTML • CSS • SASS • iQuery

FirebaseNode.jsMongoDBFigma

Adobe XD
Git & Git Hub
Agile

Languages

Arabic

English

Native

Professional

Spanish

Beginner

PROJECTS

Gold Boulevard **⊘**

Gold multi vendors e-commerce website.

Almesweak ∂

Dental clinics website.

Muslim Scholars Association **∂**

Islamic news and articles website.

Rently *⊘*

ITI Graduation Project, Real estate website.

Movies Hub *∂*

Movies application.

Weather App *⊘*

provides weather details of the current location in addition to searching for a certain location.

Nest Market ∂

E-commerce website.